<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Defs>
    <QuestScriptDef>
        <defName>VFED_ShuttleStagingPost</defName>
	    <rootSelectionWeight>2</rootSelectionWeight>
	    <expireDaysRange>3</expireDaysRange>
	    <questNameRules>
		    <rulesStrings>
			    <li>questName->Shuttle staging post</li>
		    </rulesStrings>
	    </questNameRules>
	    <questDescriptionRules>
		    <rulesStrings>
			    <li>questDescription->Our intel allowed us to pinpoint the location of a shuttle staging post belonging to [empire_name]. These staging posts allow shuttles to refuel between destinations. Destroying it will greatly hinder the Empire’s ability to freely travel the planet and resupply their forward bases.
\nWe may be able to trigger a chain detonation of the fuel containers to create havoc and make our job easier.
\nWe might find some useful supplies scattered around the staging post. If we have the time, we should take what we can.
\nThe shuttle staging post is protected by:
[forces_description]
\nWe have also been informed that the location is protected by a number of ground-mounted striker turrets. Despite the limited range, these turrets can easily reveal our approach and provide covering fire for the imperial army.
\nThe staging post is protected by surveillance pillars. They should not be approached, and instead should be disabled from afar - either by destroying them, or cutting off their power. Once activated, they will greatly increase our visibility.
\nThe objective of this assignment is to destroy all fuel containers. Once that is done, the reward will arrive and we will have to make our escape.
\nOnce we arrive at the staging post, we can expect an imperial response if our visibility is high enough. We will only have a limited amount of time to complete the mission.</li>
		    </rulesStrings>
	    </questDescriptionRules>
	    <root Class="QuestNode_SubScript">
			<def>VFED_DeserterQuestBase</def>
			<parms>
				<sitePartDef>VFED_ShuttleStagingPost</sitePartDef>
				<hasObjectives>true</hasObjectives>
				<objectiveDef>VFED_FuelTank</objectiveDef>
			</parms>
			<returnVarNames>
				<li>empire</li>
			</returnVarNames>
	    </root>
		<modExtensions>
			<li Class="VFED.QuestExtension_Deserter" />
		</modExtensions>
    </QuestScriptDef>
</Defs>