<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <VFED.Detonate>Detonate</VFED.Detonate>
    <VFED.IntelOutOfDate>Intel will go out of date in: {0}</VFED.IntelOutOfDate>
    <VFED.IntelOutOfDateNow>{0} has gone out of date. Consider using up the intel you gather before it goes out of date.</VFED.IntelOutOfDateNow>
    <VFED.SwitchTo>Click to switch to {0}</VFED.SwitchTo>
    <VFED.SurveillancePillarActivated>You have activated an imperial surveillance pillar. Visibility of your faction has increased by {1}. It is now {0}.</VFED.SurveillancePillarActivated>
    <VFED.IntelFromTitle>{0} has been stripped from their title of {1}. They have provided you with {2} Intel.</VFED.IntelFromTitle>
    <VFED.ResponseComing>Imperial response</VFED.ResponseComing>
    <VFED.ResponseComingDesc>An imperial {0} is on its way to this location. It will arrive in {1}s.</VFED.ResponseComingDesc>
    <VFED.ResponseMessage>Due to triggering an imperial response, your visibility has increased by {0}. It is now {1}. In the future, you can avoid increasing the visibility by completing the mission before the response arrives.</VFED.ResponseMessage>
    <VFED.Detonate.BombPack>Detonate bomb pack</VFED.Detonate.BombPack>
    <VFED.Detonate.BombPack.Desc>Detonate this bomb pack remotely to generate a big explosion. WARNING: Pressing this button will immediately set off the bomb.</VFED.Detonate.BombPack.Desc>
    <VFED.Deploy>Deploy</VFED.Deploy>
    <VFED.Deploy.Desc>Deploy this {0} to create a {1} at this location.</VFED.Deploy.Desc>
    <VFED.EnableInvisibility>Enable Invisibility</VFED.EnableInvisibility>
    <VFED.EnableInvisibility.Desc>Turn this colonist invisible for 1 hour. If the colonist attacks anyone, the invisibility will end.</VFED.EnableInvisibility.Desc>
    <VFED.OnCooldown>On cooldown</VFED.OnCooldown>
    <VFED.AlreadyInvisibile>Already invisible</VFED.AlreadyInvisibile>
    <VFED.MustHavePsylink>Must have psylink</VFED.MustHavePsylink>
    <VFED.ExtractIntel>Extract intel</VFED.ExtractIntel>
    <VFED.ExtractIntel.Desc>Extract intel from the brain of a nobleperson. They may be alive, dead, or downed, but the brain must be present. Will destroy the brain.</VFED.ExtractIntel.Desc>
    <VFED.ImperialPatrol>{0} patrol</VFED.ImperialPatrol>
    <VFED.ImperialPatrol.Desc>{0} has encountered an imperial patrol from {1}. They have been spotted! {0} can try and escape, but this will inevitably increase the visibility of {2}. Fighting the patrol might be tough, but it will keep {2} safe. The patrol consists of:\n\n{3}</VFED.ImperialPatrol.Desc>
    <VFED.ImperialPatrol.Escape>Escape the patrol.</VFED.ImperialPatrol.Escape>
    <VFED.ImperialPatrol.Attack>Attack the patrol.</VFED.ImperialPatrol.Attack>
    <VFED.ImperialPatrol.GiveUp>Give up {0}.</VFED.ImperialPatrol.GiveUp>
    <VFED.ImperialPatrol.GaveUp>{0} has given up {1} to the Empire. It’s unlikely you will ever see them again. Empire doesn’t take kindly to saboteurs.</VFED.ImperialPatrol.GaveUp>
    <VFED.AerodroneBombardment>Aerodrone bombardment</VFED.AerodroneBombardment>
    <VFED.AerodroneBombardment.Desc>The {0} has dispatched a number of aerodrones to your location. They suspect you are harboring deserters with ill intention towards the Great Hierarchy.
An aerodrone is an unmanned atmospheric drone designed for military purposes. Controlled by highly skilled warprogrammers from imperial installations, the aerodrone is a highly effective tool for eliminating enemies of the Empire. Equipped with advanced sensors and targeting systems, the aerodrone can detect and track targets from great distances. Once a target has been identified, the aerodrone will unleash a devastating salvo of precision rockets, each one designed to cause maximum damage and destruction.
The Empire has pinpointed the location of your critical infrastructure and the aerodrones will shortly initiate their bombardment. Evacuation is advised.</VFED.AerodroneBombardment.Desc>
    <VFED.GlassingDate>Glassing date</VFED.GlassingDate>
    <VFED.DivineInferno.Init>Divine Inferno initiated</VFED.DivineInferno.Init>
    <VFED.DivineInferno.Desc>The Orbital Slicer Beam satellites have finished arranging into a beautiful flower pattern above your colony. What comes next can only be described as total destruction. The slicer beams fire down from the sky, creating a web of energy that systematically levels everything in its path. The terrain itself seems to buckle and heave as the beams slice through the earth, leaving behind deep crevices and rubble-filled craters. People, vehicles, and even buildings are reduced to nothing more than dust and ash in a matter of seconds. The air itself is superheated by the intense energy of the beams, creating a blast wave that can travel for miles.
There is no escape from the Divine Inferno. Those caught in its path are instantly vaporized, leaving behind nothing but charred remnants of what was once there. Even underground shelters are no match for the destructive power of the slicer beams, as they cut through the earth like a hot knife through butter.
The aftermath of Divine Inferno is a wasteland of destruction. The landscape is unrecognizable, with little more than rubble and ash as far as the eye can see. The air is still thick with the acrid smell of burnt flesh and melting metal. The once-thriving colony is now nothing more than a scorched and lifeless husk.</VFED.DivineInferno.Desc>
    <VFED.GoodwillDropVisibility>Due to imperial disinformation, your relations with {0} have dropped by 10.</VFED.GoodwillDropVisibility>
    <VFED.ShotsFiredLeft>{0} beams fired, {1} beams left</VFED.ShotsFiredLeft>
    <VFED.VisibilityIncreases>Visibility increases by {0}</VFED.VisibilityIncreases>
    <VFED.VisibilityDecreases>Visibility decreases by {0}</VFED.VisibilityDecreases>
    <VFED.VisibilityIncreases.Desc>Visibility will increase by {0}. This may lead to more and stronger imperial responses.</VFED.VisibilityIncreases.Desc>
    <VFED.VisibilityDecreases.Desc>Visibility will decrease by {0}. This may reduce imperial responses.</VFED.VisibilityDecreases.Desc>
    <VFED.BiosecuredCrateWarning>Biosecured crates can only be opened by characters with a noble backstory.</VFED.BiosecuredCrateWarning>
    <VFED.CantOpenBiosecured>requires noble backstory</VFED.CantOpenBiosecured>
    <VFED.ServiceIncreasedGoodwill>Goodwill with {0} increased by 5 due to positive rumors from imperial deserters.</VFED.ServiceIncreasedGoodwill>
    <VFED.DetectedWarning>You have been detected by security. The garrision is deploying against you.</VFED.DetectedWarning>
    <VFED.HighAlertWarning>The defenders are moving to high alert.</VFED.HighAlertWarning>
    <VFED.FleeWarning>{0} is attempting to escape!</VFED.FleeWarning>
    <VFED.NobleKilledRevenge>{0} from {1} are attempting to avenge {2}.</VFED.NobleKilledRevenge>
    <VFED.ContrabandArrived>Your contraband has arrived.</VFED.ContrabandArrived>
    <VFED.VisibilityChange>Visibility Changed: {0}</VFED.VisibilityChange>
    <VFED.VisibilityChange.Desc>Your visibility level has changed. It is now {0}.</VFED.VisibilityChange.Desc>
    <VFED.VisibilityEffectsActive>The following effects have activated:</VFED.VisibilityEffectsActive>
    <VFED.VisibilityEffectsInactive>The following effects have deactivated:</VFED.VisibilityEffectsInactive>
</LanguageData>